Hi everyone, Priscilla here with Communal Press. I wanted to do a quick check-in. As you know,
we were in Cuba just a few months ago delivering much-needed aid, and we have another opportunity
for that to support the people in Cuba. So IFCO Pastors for Peace is planning to send over 60,000
pounds of aid. That's around 200 boxes in a shipment container. So they are raising $50,000
to make that possible. So the money is going to go towards assembling and shipping hundreds of boxes
with essential medicines and vitamins, medical equipment, surgical supplies, contraceptives,
feminine hygiene products, non-perishable pantry items, bicycles, school supplies. If you've been
looking for an organization to donate to and support the people in Cuba who are on the ground
doing the work, I highly recommend that you donate to IFCO, and that's at ifconews.org forward slash
shipment. As you know, Cuba is currently under attack. We are calling for the end of the embargo
and to the blockade and to let Cuba live.